sixpackfactory.com 2012-05-22

# Abs Nutrition, Abs Workout Diet, Diet For Six Pack Abs | SixPackFactory.com

This Privacy Policy sets out the approach which Sixpackfactory will take in relation to the treatment of Personal Information.

### **Collection**

Sixpackfactory will only collect Personal Information where the information is necessary to perform one or more of its functions or activities. In this context, “collect” means gather, acquire or obtain by any means, information in circumstances where the individual is identifiable or identified. Sixpackfactory collects Personal Information primarily to supply users with the products and services provided by this site and its related companies. Sixpackfactory also collects and uses Personal Information for secondary purposes including billing and account management. Sixpackfactory will not collect Sensitive Information from individuals except with consent and only where it is necessary for Loveclients to collect such information for an activity or function.

### **Use**

Sixpackfactory will obtain an individual’s consent for use of non-sensitive Personal Information for Secondary Purposes at the time of collection, unless the Use is a related Secondary Purpose which would be within Sixpackfactory Uses Personal Information primarily for the purposes listed ABOVE. If Sixpackfactory relies on the Direct Marketing exception to Direct Market to individuals it will ensure that: the individual is clearly notified of their right to Opt Out from further Direct Marketing; and if the individual Opts Out of all Direct Marketing the Opt Out will be respected by Sixpackfactory. Sixpackfactory will not use Sensitive Information for Direct Marketing. Sixpackfactory will not use Personal Information without taking reasonable steps to ensure that the information is accurate, complete and up to date.

### **Disclosure**

Sixpackfactory may Disclose Personal Information to unrelated third parties to enable outsourcing of functions (such as billing, customer relations management and order fulfillment), where that is Disclosure or Use for a related Secondary Purpose and has been notified to individuals or where such Disclosure is within the individual’s Reasonable Expectations.

Sixpackfactory will take reasonable steps to ensure that its contracts with third parties include requirements for third parties to comply with the Use and Disclosure requirements of the Privacy Act.

Sixpackfactory may Disclose Personal Information to law enforcement agencies, government agencies, courts or external advisers where permitted or required by law.

#### BEST OF SIX PACK FACTORY

#### Recent comments

#### Join us on Facebook
